Week Two Dom, what is domination? Okay,
so this is from the Oxford Dictionary and they say that domination is to exercise
the power or influence over someone or something or the state of being so controlled.
I believe that domination is very different on the inside, it's how it looks on the
outside. It's an exchange of trust, energy and power play between the dominant and
the submissive. What is a dominatrix? A
dominatrix, AKA Dom, is a woman who is taking the dominating role in the BDSM activities.
She usually goes by mistress and or goddess.
There are other names you can use but these they're most common too.
A good Dom has his sub's best interests at heart and she is confident and professional.
Now, she knows her worth and trusts her judgment.
She connects to her subs, forms relationships with them and she understands it's
more about the connection than to just bark orders.
She is intuitive to her subs needs and desires.
What is a submissive? A submissive is a person who takes the submissive roles
in BDSM activities. They are ready to conform to their mistresses and please
here. They are obedient, loyal and attentive.
They enjoy the power play of giving up all control to their mistress and
they want to be held in a safe space to explore their fantasies.
Okay, so let's go through the basics. In the world of domination, there's a lot to
know as there are many different types of domination and as a professional Dom, you
should have an understanding for each category but for now, let's not over complicate
it. Below is a simple step-by-step method that you can follow.
Step one, find out what type of domination your client is into.
Ask as many questions as possible. So domination can look completely different to
one sub to the next. You know, one sub could be into something really specific
and gentle, whereas another could be into a really, you know, harsh style of domination.
So this is why it's very important in the beginning to find out exactly what they're
into so you can deliver them, you know, the best possible experience.
So before you actually start your Dom session, I would ask your clients some questions
just to find out exactly what they like. So for example, I had a client the other
day told me he was owned by a previous mistress.
So I asked him, tell me more about being owned and what did that look like for you?
And he told me that being owned for him looked like going around to her house every
week and doing all of her chores. So cleaning her house for her.
So that told me that he is a service sub.
So he really likes to do tasks for his mistress.
Now, how I would change that up to cater to be online, because, you know, not
all of you are gonna wanna meet with your subs and that's fine.
So if you never wanna meet with them, yet you wanna keep him as your sub, you could
say, oh, I like the fact that you went and done your chores for your mistress.
I bet that made her really happy. I have some chores for you to do for me.
I am currently researching, you know, blah, blah, whatever it is.
I would like you to go research this topic for me and come back with the best points
and, you know, with a summary of this topic.
So that way your sub is still doing a service for you, but, you know, they're not
necessarily doing a service where they have to meet you and be in your home.
So that's how I would switch that one up.
You can also ask your subs, what are their wants and desires?
Ask open questions and stay open while listening to them.
You can ask them what type of submission they're into and if they have any experience.
Obviously, if they've not got much experience, you wanna be nice and gentle in the
beginning, but if they are more experienced, they should be able to tell you exactly
what they're into and yeah, you'll know exactly where to take the session.
You can ask them what got them into being a sub and what do they want to feel.
You can ask them who is. Their ideal Dom and what do they enjoy most about the Dom
sub-relationship. You can ask them what makes them go weak and what are their limits.
This is very important. And you can also ask them who is their perfect Dom and what
does she do to them. Now if you ask these questions they are basically giving
you a you know a rule book on exactly what to do with them and how to treat
them. So the more questions you ask the better the session is going to be for them
because you're going to get more of an idea of exactly what they want and then you
can just deliver that to them if you are comfortable too.
Okay so number two on the basics is establish a safe word and limits.
Now this is basically you know it's on day one of learning how to be a Dom is
establish a safe word. It's very important to do this and yeah
if you don't do this your subs will know straight away you're not a professional
Dom because every single professional Dom will always make sure there is a safe word
before any session has started because obviously then you know you know that you're
keeping within your subs boundaries and you're not going too far as if you do they
can just use a safe word. It's also good to find out your subs limits as well because
then you can you know don't need to go to outside of their limits.
Some subs will want you to play on the border of their limits and you can gauge their
reaction and then see you know whether you should take it further or whether you
should pull back. So yeah this is why it's really important to understand your subs
limits. Number three start the session now you are in control
so once you've got some time asking your sub what they're into you've got more
of an idea of what they like you've established a safe word and limits it's now time
to start the session. Once you start the session you're not going to ask them any
questions you can definitely check in with your sub throughout and ask them and you
know how is it going how are you feeling how are you finding this you can definitely
ask those type of questions throughout just to make sure you're going in the right
track but when you're in session it's more about you being in control rather than
you know asking them how it's going it's more about you and delivering the session.
So number four while in session listen and watch how your client responds to you
and adjust the session accordingly. So if they are if
they clearly are into this and they're loving it and you know they're really attentive
and really you know you can see that they're enjoying it then just carry on in the
direction that you're going but if you feel as though they're pulling back then
I would definitely taper off a little bit and become a little bit more gentle or
maybe they're taper enough because you're not being harsh enough maybe they want
you to be even more harsh than you already are so you know if you feel as though
you're losing them throughout the session that they're not really engaging and responding
as much as they was in the beginning you can ask them how you're finding this and
you know is this going how you would usually like it to go and they might say
oh actually no I normally like to be put on my place a little bit more or I usually
like it a little bit harsher than that then you'll know to you know up the ante a
little bit so although we do most of the questions in the beginning it's still okay
to check in throughout because at the end of the day we are here delivering a service
to your clients so we want to make sure we're delivering the best possible service
so they come back time and time again and trust me if you deliver a good service
to the subs they will come back and they will be loyal and they will spend and this
is exactly what we want okay so number five debrief
ask your clients how they felt during the session during the session and how they
feel now what did your client like and dislike about it so this
also is very important and so yeah at the end of the session I always ask my clients
how did you find that what did you enjoy about it and with any points that you didn't
enjoy was it anything that you know really stuck out to you that you know didn't
think that you would enjoy but you did and yeah just really get an idea of how it
went for them and I would then write it down so keep a little note
of each client and you can write next to each client's name a little bit about how
the session went and what they enjoyed and what you might try with them next time
that way when they come back into your chat next time you don't have to do step one
so much again you don't have to ask a million questions yeah you can still ask some
questions in the beginning but you've already established that this client is into
this this and this and isn't into this this and this so you don't need to go over
the same things again as what I'm saying you can just go even deeper into the knowledge
of them and what they're into and what they like you can even explore it even further
now that you have a basic understanding you can go even deeper which is great
and in this moment you can also tell your client how you felt and you
know how happy you was throughout the session because they were being really attentive
and really submissive or you can tell them you know I didn't like it in the session
when you didn't do as you were asked when you didn't do this or when you said this
because to me that was a disrespect to your mistress so next time don't do that so
you can always you know tell them how you felt and tell them how they can improve
in the future and if you follow the steps above it
will ensure for a safe and enjoyable session for both your clients and yourself your
client will feel they're in the safe hands of an experienced dominatrix playing
within the boundaries we've already spoken about staying
within your subs boundaries but theirs aren't the only ones that you need to consider
sticking to your own boundaries and only doing areas of domination that you are comfortable
with is also very important you don't need to offer every
aspect of domination as they'll be part of domination that don't feel right to you
and don't sit right with your soul and that's okay so I've done this for ten years
now and I have definitely explored many different types of domination
and there are a few that I've not even considered to explore because I already
know that will not sit right with me for example racial humiliation is
a part of domination that some clients enjoy this is something I have never ever
looked at because I know already I'm not going to be into that and that's okay you
don't have to offer everything to every single sub and you know maybe
there are some parts of domination that you're not sure if you would enjoy or not
so it's definitely okay to try it and try out things that you know you're not sure
on but then if you try it and it's not for you never do that again even if your sub
is asking you can tell them oh I don't actually offer that area of domination but
there are many dominatrix's on this website who do go have
a session with them and report back to me how it was so that way hopefully you are
keeping the client because they will come back to you and report to their mistress
how their other mistress was and then yeah that way you're sticking within
your own boundaries you're not doing anything that you are not comfortable with yet
your sub is still living out you know the fantasies that they want to live out and
enjoy and without you know putting yourself in a position that you are not feeling
comfortable and so yes that's what I would do there and it's like I said it's totally
okay to say no you don't have to offer it all and your subs will respect that and
they'll probably respect you even more because you have told them no actually I don't
do that so yeah just tell them you know you don't offer that go and
do that with somebody else and come back and tell me exactly how it was okay so
Elle wrote a comment about the previous side she said I also like to tell my clients
how I found it at the end and if you're chatting as they often like to know that
you enjoyed it and feed off your enjoyment that's so true I didn't actually even
mention that and they love to know they are pleasing their mistress they absolutely
love it I mean that's what they're for at the end of the day is to do what we ask
and do what we tell them so if you're telling them you know you've been such a good
sub today you've really pleased your mistress today they're gonna love that so you
know of course you can be harsh as well and you can tell them oh no don't do that
again you didn't do that right or you know oh next time I hope you do it better I
don't know you can did you like to also be put in the place as well and told like
you know do it better and then they'll thrive off the fact that they have then done
it again to then do it even better to please you even further you know and but yeah
always letting them know that they're pleasing you by doing what they've been told
and being an attentive sub it does really um they do really love that Okay,
so common types of domination. There are many different types of domination as we
discovered earlier. It's important to find out what each sub is into, as being dominated
can look completely different from one sub to the next.
So let's take a look at some of the most common types of domination.
Foot and body worship. Okay, so this is very, very common, especially
foot worship. Don't know if you guys were like, maybe just in your normal lives,
I've had guys message you in your inbox, like asking for pictures of your feet.
I definitely have and I've not even, you know, what
happened there? Can everyone hear me? I don't know what happened.
I think it might
have boosted us out, but we're back. Okay, okay.
Is everyone back and can everyone hear me?
Yeah? Okay, so I don't know what happened there.
Yeah, so foot and body worship, it's very, very popular.
And body worship actually could be one, another one that is quite gentle
for any new subs to start with. So if you get anyone coming into your chat that is
quite new to this and they want to try domination, you could do body worship because
let's be honest, most people are going to be into that.
Not everyone's going to be into, you know, cock and ball torture or something like
that straight off the bat. But a lot of guys would be into body worship.
So basically body worship is them just worshiping your body.
So that could just be your body with your beautiful dom outfit on, or it could be
parts of your body that are a bit more naked, depending on what you are comfortable
with. But to be honest, it could literally just be you in a beautiful dom outfit
or just any outfit, you know, any outfit will do.
It doesn't need to be a dom style outfit.
And yeah, like they are just going to be telling you about your body, how amazing
it is, how beautiful you are as their dom, as their mistress.
So yeah, that's a big, you know, a big one for people.
It's very popular. And footwareship, it's a little bit more specific.
So, you know, they will tell you that they're into feet and then you can just, you
know, put your feet in the cam, let them look at your feet.
You can maybe even oil your feet, put some oil on, do a little massage on your feet
and they will love it. And they will tell you how amazing your feet are and that
they would like to be at your feet worshiping you, you know.
So this is quite an intro one, I would say.
And by the way, all of these different types of domination, we actually do have
more information of them on the website. So if you want to learn more about any of
them, we have them on our website, but of course you can also Google as well and
just delve even deeper into knowing about all of it.
Okay, so another common type of domination is small penis humiliation, slash
any humiliation in general. So this one, when I first started, I was like, as if
that's even a thing, like people like to be taken the piss out of because they've
got a small penis, like what? But trust me, it is also very popular.
A lot of them like it. And sometimes they show you their penis and
it's not even small. And you're like, it's actually not small.
So like, I don't know. It's weird that they're into it, but not weird.
Actually, we don't want to discriminate, but you know, it's odd to me that they're
into small penis humiliation, but they've actually got a big one, but maybe that's
all part of it. Who knows? Everyone's got their fantasies for all different reasons.
We are just there to guide them through the experience.
But with small penis humiliation, some things you can do is you can ask them, you
know, is it this big? Or you can do this to them.
Like, you know, be like this when you do this, like, oh, it's just like a little,
just small, like my little finger. You can ask them if when they want their dick,
do they have to do this because it's so small.
And yeah, just stuff like that. But again, this is super popular.
So if you are happy to offer this, I would learn, you know, some phrases and stuff
that you could say to them because they love it.
A lot of small penis humiliation clients also like the thought of knowing that you
are laughing about their small penis with your friends.
They will tell you. Oh, what would your friends say if they seen this?
Would you guys all laugh at me? So they want to hear, yeah, we would all laugh at
you. Oh my God, we've all, I've just showed my friends because sometimes they say,
you know, take a photo and show your friends.
Obviously you don't have to do that. But I just say, oh, I've just sent the photo
in the group chat. Everyone's replying, laughing at you.
They can't believe how small it is. Ha ha ha.
We'll all have a laugh about this next time we meet up and they genuinely like thrive
off the fact that you're laughing at them.
And so, yeah, that's small penis humiliation.
And then there's also other types of humiliation as well.
They'll tell you what they're into. And again, if it's something that you're, don't
feel comfortable to offer, just tell them, no, I don't offer that.
Okay, so JOI / edging. So jerk off instruction and edging.
They are two different things, but they kind of go together.
So jerk off instruction is obviously telling them exactly how to touch themselves.
And then edging is where you will bring them to the point where
they're about to orgasm. And then you'll stop and make them stop so they don't.
And you'll keep doing that. You'll bring them closer, bring them to the edge basically,
and then stop. So yeah, that's another type of domination.
And even though, you know, it does kind of go with jerk off instruction, but maybe
someone will just want you to just edge them the whole time.
And then it's up to you, whether you let them come or not at the end.
If they've been really good and obedient, then maybe you can let them.
Or maybe you're feeling really savage that day and you don't let them come and you
tell them to keep it and do not come until the next time they come to chat with you.
So you could say, you know, I don't want you to come, I want you to hold it so it's
even more powerful next time. I want you to save it for your mistress and say that
kind of stuff. And then of course, you'll plan to see them, you know, again over
the next few days. And then that time you will let them or not.
You can just be really mean and just keep it going even longer.
Okay, so another type of domination is findom, which is financial domination.
Now this one is a personal favourite of mine because, you
know, you can make a lot of money with this.
So financial domination is basically clients coming into your chat room
and they basically wanna give you their money because they believe, well,
in this moment of the power play, their scenario in their head is that they believe
you are more deserving of their money. Their mistress is way more deserving and,
you know, they wanna send it all to you. So you could have them do this by tipping
you on cam. So of course they're paying, you know, per minute to be in your chat.
But with financial domination, it's more than just a per minute.
You need to like, you can ask them to tip you because you deserve it and they don't.
Some things you would say to financial domination clients is you would call them
a pay pig, a human ATM, piggy, you know, stuff like this.
It's all falls under financial domination.
I actually had a client once who gave me this login to his
computer. There was this like, I think it was called team viewer or something like
that that I had to download. And he put in a certain code and it allows me to access
his computer. And he had his banking, like banking thing open.
He wanted me to go into his bank and watch me send the money from his bank to mine.
Like actually like couldn't do that now because it's all changed.
I don't work properly, I don't even know.
Saying that maybe they would, who knows. I'm wondering if they would even allow you
to still do that. But back in the day, things were a lot more lenient than they are
now. And yeah, he just wanted me to sit there and watch me transfer the money from
his account to mine. And that's what they're into.
A lot of Fintan clients will be into cash point meets.
Of course, you know, maybe a lot of you won't offer that, but they will definitely
fantasise about that. Go into a cash point, taking out money and hand it straight
to you. That's something they'll fantasise about.
So although you might not actually do that, I've never actually done that.
I've spoke about that a lot to clients. I've said, you know, what I'll wear when
I meet them. You know, I've just spoke about the scenario in
detail. And that's a lot of what this is as well, domination.
It's not necessarily always telling them what to do.
It's talking about the fantasy. It's basically explaining like how it would work,
you know. If you were to meet up and do this cash point meet, or if you were to meet
up and use a dildo on them or whatever, even though
if you're never gonna do that, they wanna just talk about this and like explore that,
you know? Okay, and we have more about all of this on the website.
Okay, so another type of domination is basically like clothing fetish.
So latex, leather, stockings, tights, that kind of stuff, heels.
So yeah, that's another type of it. They like to see you in these outfits.
So I remember, well, I've got a few guys actually that I just, they just sit there,
I put an outfit on out of the camera cause I don't like let them see me naked like
a lot of the subs. I put an outfit on, come back, show them and they'll be like,
you know, tell me how amazing the outfit is.
Spend a few minutes doing that. Go off camera, put an outfit on, come back.
And before you know it, it's been like an hour or so and you've just been trying
on outfits, doing a fashion show for these clients basically.
So this one can be quite easy and fun, especially if you've got a lot of outfits.
So yeah, again, just another type of domination.
You can tell them how the leather or latex or stockings or whatever it is, how it
feels on your skin. If you put your mic on, even if you don't talk, you can put your
mic on and you can rub over your body part that you're wearing the outfit and they'll
be able to hear, especially if it's latex, they'll be able to hear the sounds of
the rubber. So, you know, you can incorporate that.
So it's not just a visual, they're also getting the audio as well of how it actually
sounds. So yeah, that's another type. Okay,
and another one we have is CP which is corporal punishment.
So this is like spanking, whipping, you know, stuff like that.
So you can obviously direct them how to spank themselves.
Maybe if you even have a whip yourself around, you can like have the whip in your
hand and, you know, act as like, you know, obviously not gonna actually use it, but
just, you know, just them seeing you hold a whip with like in your like dominating
presence, they would really love that. Sissification
is another type of domination. And this is basically where the client likes to dress
as a woman. So sometimes I will open up my stubs camera and they've got better hair
and makeup done than me because a lot of the time I don't really bother with my hair
and makeup so much. Sometimes they're sat there like full face, smokey eye and I'm
like, oh my God, give me some makeup tips.
So yeah, some clients are really into that.
So, you know, you will know like obviously in your beginning questions when you start
to ask the client what they're into, they'll have told you, oh yeah, I actually like
putting my wife's underwear on from time to time.
I like wearing a thong to the office, you know, see if anyone would notice.
I really like how it feels cause they like how it feels cause it feels differently
than wearing boxies, right? Like having a thong on.
And yeah, you can even ask them makeup tips.
Like genuinely you can, like, you know, you can say, oh, your makeup looks great
today. Like how'd like talk me through how you've done it.
They would love to tell you. It's almost like you're chatting with a girlfriend kind
of thing. And yeah, like sometimes they'll have a wig on, wear their wife's clothes.
You can ask them to dress up in different things for you.
You can ask them how it makes them feel, you know, what if, or how would it make
you feel if you were at work and you bend forward and somebody see in the back of
your thong and you like peek out your pants, how would that make you feel, you know?
So stuff like that, just be creative with it.
And finally, another type of like domination, you
know, is basically a specific role play for each client.
So even though there are many different types of domination, many more than I've
mentioned there, there's a lot, you know, this, the stuff that I don't even like
to delve into, for example, racial humiliation or like racial domination.
That's a thing, but I don't like to touch that personally.
But there is so more other than that, like so much more than that.
But the main thing to do is basically just find out what each individual client likes.
So, you know, you might have a guy who's into Finn Dom,
but it might've all stemmed from something in the past.
And his thing about Finn Dom might be like, I don't know, his auntie taking his money
when he was a kid or something like that.
So he might like to call you auntie while he's doing it.
So even though he's into findom, his little twist on it is that you are playing
the auntie role, if that makes sense. So yeah, everyone's got their fetishes and what
they're into, but then a lot of the clients as well have their own little twist on
it, which is only, would only work with them.
So as I was saying earlier, you know, you can't just do the same thing, same type,
sorry, you can't just offer the same type of domination to everyone because everyone's
gonna be different. It gets even more individual when they have their own little
spin that they put on it. And again, this is something to note down.
So if any of them do ever have little quirks to their domination, just, or how they
like to be dominated, I should say, just note it down and then next time, you know,
you'll know exactly what to offer them. Okay, so we went through the common types
of domination. Has anyone got any questions at this point?
Would you say like, because is it required, do you think to like get like a wear,
and you know, like get specific like costumes and stuff?
Or would you say like, don't bother doing that until?
Well, yeah, to be honest, you don't like, this actually was something I was gonna
touch on as well. The domination, it's not about the clothes that you're wearing.
Even in my profile picture, for example, even though my profile is written about
a lot of pater to a Dom, like a sub, it's catered to a lot of like sub clients.
Even my profile picture, I'm just wearing a bikini.
It's not a Dom photo at all. Maybe my look as a Dom look, I look quiet, but the actual
outfit itself isn't. And I don't always go online and leather and latex, especially
when it's a hot day here in Australia, I'm not gonna be sat in a latex, like, you
know, so it's not always about what you're wearing, is what I'm trying to say.
It's about the experience that you're providing and your energy.
But with that being said, of course, if you are, you know, getting into this more
and more, and it's something that you're offering and more and more subs are coming
through, then I definitely would, you know, have a few outfits that you could wear,
have like a whip here and like, you know, stuff like that, but it's not necessary.
It's definitely not necessary, but it will add to it in the future if you end up,
you know, really investing your time and energy into this.
But yeah, domination, it's more about a mindset and the energy that you are putting
out rather than what's actually on your body.
Yeah, any more questions? No, okay, I'll
carry on. Okay, so
the different types of submissives. Not
all of your subs are going to show up the same for many different reasons.
Some subs may have more time to commit to this, whereas others you may only see every
couple of months. Some may have been exploring this world for 20 years or more, whereas
others may have only just started delving into this and you're their very first experience
of being domed. So I actually had a guy, a sub who came to
me and I was his first ever time that he'd been domed.
And I feel like there's something special about that.
They kind of get latched on when you're there first, like, you know, they never go
away. Like even though now I don't, the type of domination he's into, like he wants
to be dominated online, but then also meet up with the sub and be pegged by them.
So be like fucked with a strap-on basically.
And I'm not gonna offer that to him and he knows that.
So again, I don't want to said earlier, I said, go away to another mistress, do
your thing, report back to me. And this is what he does.
So even though I'm not giving him, you know, exactly what he wants with the pegging,
of course, I'm still there as one of his doms, you know, hearing what he did with
the other mistress, doing our own session.
So yeah, that's him. So just remember that is always something that you don't offer.
Just send them away to come back. And yet if you are that sub's first experience
of a dominatrix, they'll probably be latched on to you for life.
Okay, so you got the subset are new to this, they're nervous and needs to be eased
in gently. So we've already spoke about what you could do with them.
You could do some body worship and maybe some jerk-off instruction.
So I feel like these are quite entry-level, it's nothing too crazy, you know?
And again, most people are gonna enjoy this, you know, looking at a beautiful woman
while being told how to touch themselves.
It's quite, I think it is quite a good entry-level thing to do with them.
So you'll also get some clients coming in who are semi-experienced, so they're still
very open and curious. So they've done this a little bit here and there, but they're
still exploring a further to see, what other aspects of domination they would like.
And you will also get the veterans who know exactly what they want and they don't
want it any other way. So you get the subs who've done this a lot and they say, yeah,
I'm into this, this and this. And this is what I want basically, and which I actually
quite like, I like it when it's like that, because then I know that experience, so
I know I'm not gonna end up pushing them too far.
And then when they tell me exactly what they want, it just makes our job easier because
it takes off the guessing. They tell you, I'm into this, this and this.
Then you know, oh yeah, okay, findom, okay, Piggy.
Oh, little Piggy, how have you been? Or you can just go to your, and like
go to your knowledge of that subject and deliver that to them.
So you'll get the clients as well who just dip in and out of it.
So, you know, maybe you'll see them one day and then you won't see them again for
another couple of weeks or months or maybe even years.
And so obviously they're ones who are not so serious, they like to just do it every
now and again. You'll also get your subs that have regular
arranged sessions. So, you know, you might have one that you see every Wednesday
at 6 p.m. Or, you know, one that every time at the end of one session you arrange
your next one, which is great. I like to do this because then of course, it, you
know, remains, it means repeat business and that's what you want.
You want them to just keep coming back and you'll get your devoted
loyal subs who literally are there week in, week out, who, you know,
are just, yeah, under your care, under your supervision and guidance and yeah,
I think this can be nice because you start to really develop a relationship with
them. And like I said, it's not, like I've said a few times now it's not just about
calling the shots. You know, you're really getting to know this person, what makes
them tick. And yeah, it can be a really beautiful relationship believe it or not.
From the outside people might think that sounds crazy, you know, as a dumbness, a
sub and a dom, like, you know, the dom just must be this evil person who's inflicting
like pain and you know, bad answer to this person.
It's not like that, you know, it can be a really lovely relationship and both parties
are benefiting from the relationship. And then of course, you'll get your time
wasters. So a lot of the time, these are the people in your email inbox who are just
in there telling you, you know, about all their fantasies and whatnot, which is fine.
But then when you try and get them into a private chat they're, it's like tumbleweed.
So just steer clear of those ones. I definitely would reply to emails.
Sometimes if they've sent me like a really lengthy email, don't feel like you have
to send a lengthy one back because you know, time is money and you're not being paid
for that. So whenever I get any kind of an email, I always, if
it's something I would offer, I always say, oh yeah, you know, JOI, I love
that, I love telling someone exactly how to like, how to touch themselves and be
like, blah, blah, blah. Why don't you come into my private chat today and we'll go
through a session, something like that. That's, I will leave it at that.
If they come back again and again and again, email back and forth, like, you know,
they're never gonna come and spend, these are just freeloaders, so just be aware.
But that's not just with Domination, any type of webcam and you're gonna get freeloaders
in your inbox. Don't get me wrong, some guys in the inbox are great.
They like to make the initial contact via inbox and make sure you offer what they
want, which I actually really like and respect.
And then they'll come into your private chat.
So don't write everyone off who's in your inbox is what I'm saying.
Just give everyone the time of day. But once you give them the time of day and they've
not came into your private, that's where it ends.
I would recommend anyway. Okay,
so let's take a look at subs versus slaves versus simps.
Has anyone ever heard of a simp, by the way?
This is quite a new expression. Well, semi-new.
Again, another lovely photo from our photo shoot.
Okay, so slaves are a little different to your usual sub and
norm- A normal sub, whatever normal is, will want a session with you, and that's
where it begins and ends. So, yeah, they'll have the session, you know, and then
that ends it. And then you see them again next time, you don't hear from them in
between. A slave, however, will want much more.
They are way more dedicated, and can even go as far as becoming a full-time slave
to their mistress by signing a contract. So, obviously, these are just, you know,
it's not like the contract, it's not something that's actually real, if that makes
sense. It's just more for their fantasy. So, you can actually get contracts online
for slaves and send it to them and have them sign it and send you it back.
So, yeah, a slave, obviously, is someone more who is fully dedicated to you and committed
to you. These are definitely the type of clients that you will ask to do tasks with
you outside of camp. So, you can tell them, you know, I want you to...
It could even be something that is like, you know, enjoyable for them.
Like, I want you to touch yourself tonight before you go to bed and think about me.
Think about, you know, you being at my feet and kissing my feet while I'm above you.
You know, if they're into feet, that's what you would say.
So, yeah, you can have them perform, do things outside of the session.
But, yeah, some slaves will want to do even more.
They'll want to be really dedicated and committed to you.
And, you know, you don't have to actually take on that responsibility either as a
dom. If you don't want that, you can just, you know, tell them you don't want to
own anyone at the moment. You've already got a couple of subs that you own.
You've got no space for any more. Or you can just say you're taking off time from
actually doing that. You're just more offered in the sessions one-on-one.
But if you do have someone who wants to sign a contract and become a little bit more
committed to you, this is good because, you know, they're going to be a regular loyal
client then. They're going to keep coming back.
And the weird slaves, it actually... It doesn't sound worse
than what it actually is. It's not like they're actually a slave, you know what I
mean? It's like they are basically just a more dedicated sub.
That's how I would put it. And simps. So this
is like a newer term. I'll read this out and then I'll go into a bit of detail about
it. So a simp, however, is a newer term, which is a slang insult for
men who are seen as too attentive and too submissive to women, especially out
of the failed hope of winning some sexual attention from them, even though they know
they will never get the woman's attention unless there is money involved.
So many of the OnlyFans girls, you actually see them on Twitter and stuff like that
asking for simps. They'll say, any simps around today?
And these women, they're not necessarily doms.
They're just, you know, they're not portraying themselves as a dom.
But a simp, it's more of like a new world in like pop culture, which basically
describes someone who's really, you know, trying to get the attention from you.
So this is a little bit different to your usual sub because they might not necessarily
be into domination. These guys, they might not want to be told they've got a small
penis or this or that, but they just like to worship you and give you attention.
And I actually have a client like this, this guy, Johnny.
I don't actually dom him. He just comes into my chat and he's literally just obsessed.
Like he just comes back. Like, you know, I'm sure he's like this with many of the
girls on there. He's just so, yeah, when he's there, he's just always like, you're
just so beautiful. You're there. Like he's, you know, even though I'm not putting
him in his place as he's a sub, there is a dominant slash submissive role between
us both. So yeah, Simp would be the guys who just come in, shower
you in attention, shower you in compliments, shower you in love.
And then you'll just accept them, like, you know, accept the compliments or whatever
else, but you won't necessarily dom them.
So these are still classed as subs in my eyes because they know that they're
their submissive role, but you're not actually going through a full dom and sub relationship
with them. And I think that brings us to the end.
Yeah. Okay. Does anyone have any questions, my darlings?
I have a question. Like, during like the session, do
you have to like talk to them in a kind of mean way, like all the time?
Or is there like normal conversation as well?
Yeah. That sounds a bit weird. No, it doesn't.
It doesn't. To be honest, like. My style of domination has changed so much.
I used to be a lot more harsh, but it's now I do like to just have normal conversations
too. Like, you know, it's not about just being mean the whole time.
But when you are having like those normal conversations with them, like still keeping
the back of your mind that they're a sub.
So if you act too like, if you act too nice to them, sometimes
they don't like it. They want you to stay in that dominating presence because that's
why they're there. You know what I mean? And if you think about it right, this
is what they're into. This is what they enjoy.
A lot of these clients, they come from high power, successful business roles.
So some of them are really like, you know, amazing doctors or lawyers or even judges
in the court. I've had a lot of judges come through.
They're in really stressful jobs. So they do this.
They like to be a sub, to let go of control and just be in the hands of somebody
else's care. And they don't have to think in this moment.
They just like let go and just let their DOM, you know, do as necessary.
So for them, they actually love it when you're just, you know, in control.
So even if you're not being mean, let's say they just like for you to be in control.
They don't want to feel as though they have to think.
They just want to, you know, let go and have you direct the session.
So yeah, to answer your question, you don't have to be mean the whole time.
I really don't like to do that either. You kind of just ask normal questions about
their day, you know, like what have you been up to today?
You got any plans for the weekend? And then you can put a spin on things.
Like if they say, you know, oh, I'm going to this party or whatever, you can then
still bring it back to like the DOM sub relationship.
You could say, oh, would you wear your wife's knickers to that party and see how
that makes you feel if there's someone who does that?
Or, you know, oh, were there any beautiful women at the party that you wanted to
submit to? You know, you can like always bring it back to this subject, but
you're not necessarily just being mean the whole time.
Yeah. Makes sense. Yeah. Are you sure it doesn't make sense?
Yeah, no, it does. Yeah. Yeah. I understand.
Like you want to keep it going. You don't want to like go off track and like, you
know, be too normal. Yeah. Well, that's the thing.
But when you're in session, you definitely want to keep it like, you know, more about
being a DOM and a sub. When you're asking the questions at the start and especially
at the end, you can soften a little bit more when you're finding out if they enjoyed
it, when you're telling them how you found it.
That's when you can just be a little bit more human and soft.
Whereas when you're in session, depends on what type of domination they're into,
that's when you want to like, obviously be a little bit more powerful and, you know.
Yeah. It's really interesting, like the psychology behind it.
So interesting. I know it was, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. I think the main thing for them is that they just like to give up the power
for once in their lives. Cause honestly, a lot of these guys, they are guys who they
call the shots at their jobs. They call the shots with looking after their family
or, you know, whatever it is. So they like to just let go for a moment.
So even though you're being mean to them, they actually, they end up coming out loving
it, you know? So I know it's hard to wrap your heads around that in the beginning,
cause you're like, Oh, I'm just being mean to this.
And like, are you sure this is okay? Honestly, if they've already told you their
boundaries, you're fine. Like they, they love it.
And you're, you're giving them exactly what they want.
So I wouldn't like worry that too much about, you know, if you're being too mean
or whatever else. Cause again, you can check in with them throughout the session
as well. You can say, how are you finding this?
How, you know, how are you feeling about what I'm, what I'm saying, what I'm doing?
Like you can always check in with them throughout as well.
That's absolutely fine to do. Yeah. I find it really hard to be mean.
I actually do it in normal life, but somehow I'm like, I can't even speak.
I'm like, I can't say it. Like, it's so weird.
I think it's like conditioning from being young, like trying to be the good
girl. And like, you know, like my mum's like, over like over the top, like people
be there. So it's like, I was like trying to be mean to someone and I'm like, the
words just don't come out. It's really interesting.
That's not a bad problem to have though, is it?
Let's be honest, that says a lot about your beautiful character.
Yeah. I would like it to be a little bit more, you know, a surface.
So maybe it's good. Maybe it's for growth, self growth.
Yeah. I mean, this is a good start and it's one of them.
Like maybe when you start, if you do try this, just only offer like more gentle.
Of domination, the body worship, you know, edging, jerkoff instruction, that
kind of stuff, because it's not necessarily a type of domination where you need to
be mean, because obviously, you can just be like, with body worship, you can show
them a part of your body and then ask them, you know, what do you think about this
part of my body? Like, and you basically just, yeah, they're just basically worshipping
you, so you're not actually being mean. So that might be a good way to just start
domination yourself. Start with something more gentle.
And should, sorry, this is the last question.
Should you like, like, should you say that you've not done it before, if you haven't?
Or should you kind of keep that? Like, should you kind of act experienced?
Because they might not, I don't know if they will like it if it's someone that's
never done it before, they might not. Yeah, I mean, there definitely would be some
subs who only want a very experienced dominatrix, but there's also subs as well who
would actually like that. They would like that, this is one of your first experiences
of doing this because maybe they're new themselves, you know?
So honestly, I would always be honest. I would always, you don't have to say it for
the very first time or, you know, you don't have to say that if you don't want to,
but you could just say, you're just starting to explore this, this new way of camming.
As you know, you're intrigued to see how it is and you've done some training and
you want to give it a go. I would always be honest to be honest, like, because that's
the thing. Like, you can't offer something, you know, beyond what you know.
So you can't actually like fake it so much anyway.
You can, to a certain extent, obviously, but yeah, I would be honest.
And if they don't want that and they don't like it, they will leave, that's fine.
But there will be a client there who likes that.
Trust me, like, no matter what area of webcam it is, if you're honest about
what you offer and what you do and someone doesn't like it, let them leave because
you don't want to keep someone in there who you're never going to be able to please
anywhere, you know? Yeah. Thank you. Okay,
I'll see if there's any more questions in the chat.
Where can I read more about the psychological foundations of BDSM?
To be honest, I don't actually know where you could read more about that.
Actually, that book that you're reading, Maria, that's actually a good book with
that because Maria's reading a book that Elle actually bought for me a few years
ago called A Woman's Guide to Power and Bound.
Is that right? I think it's called that. And it's, yeah, yeah, it is.
Yeah, Maria's reading that one, Elle, I forgot to tell you.
And that's actually a good place to probably read about the psychology of it.
Although it doesn't go deep into the psychology of BDSM, it does, she talks about
power in versus power out. So as a dom, you'll put attention
in versus attention out, I think it is. You're putting your attention and power out.
You're putting it out onto the sub. And as the sub, your attention is in your, yeah,
so I think that's a good place to start, is that book.
How are you finding it? Yeah, I love it. I think I needed it like many years ago.
Yeah. I think every woman needs to read it.
But my question is, because I'm also trained in a narrative approach, which is an
approach in psychotherapy and community work.
So I'm kind of like thinking. Although it's clear that, okay,
so attention in, attention out, or like being in control, letting someone
control you, I'm interested more about things like humiliation, like why
would people want that? What do they experience?
Is it healing for them? Because it would also help me to decide which types of domination
I want to do. No, definitely, yeah. Because then I suppose if you
understand exactly why they like it and, you know.
Yeah, because otherwise, like I also did the course and it's amazing.
Like it's so detailed and there's so much information.
It's like very beneficial. It changed my idea of how I want to be on camp.
So yeah, I just, yeah, I just kind of like want to understand like, why are they
doing it? Maybe I should add a bit of that to the course.
I'm going to write that down actually, like more the psychology behind why they actually,
why they want it, why they enjoy it. I suppose for every client it's different, but
we, I'm sure that it's like a general rule of like, oh, they're into it because,
like I said, a lot of the time it's because they are like successful businessmen
who always in their life want to play the dom role.
So they want to just be the sub for a moment as a release, you know.
I'm sure there's a lot more we could discover as to why they're into it.
So yeah, I'll actually add a bit of that into the course.
Thanks. Yeah, go on Soph. Sorry. I
often ask guys if they've got, like when we're talking about their kinks and stuff,
I'll ask them about like, oh, do you have some childhood trauma around that?
You know, I'm interested in that kind of thing because I'm breastfeeding.
So my current, like, my main thing on time is breastfeeding and they're really into
it. And if they're like humiliation as well, a lot of them will say they weren't
breastfed by their mum. So it's like a craving in later life and all they were and,
you know, I'm really interested in that psychology side of things as well.
And I'll try and explore that with clients.
And most of them are quite open to discussing it with you because it's almost like
a therapy session for them. You know, they'd rather talk to, you know, who they consider
a beautiful woman. They're like therapists / sex person,
you know, that kind of thing. And I, yeah, I love that side of
it. And I'll explore my own stuff as well with some clients.
Yeah, definitely. Because like you said, it's a safe space for them to do that.
And it's not, it's someone who's, you know, a stranger, basically.
So that's why they can probably tell you their deepest and darkest secrets because
you don't know them. It's never going to come up in their real life by telling you
online, you know. So it's like their little, their little escape, I suppose.
Definitely. And ours, it is for me. Exactly.
Yeah, I love it. It took me some time to find what type of Dom I want to be.
But because, yeah, there was something in the beginning, maybe I was a bit harsh,
and then I came, stripped it back. And, you know, I've played with a lot of different
ways of being on there. But you'll find your own groove and what finds what is comfortable
to you in time. Elle said as well that there
is workshops and courses on Eventbrite. I think that's about what you were asking
about, Maria, about learning more about the psychology.
So I don't know if you've heard of Eventbrite, but yeah, they've got courses on there,
apparently. Thank you. Thank you. There's also an in-person seed
talk called Psychology of Fetish Kink that talks, oh, that talks around
comedy clubs. That'd be interesting to listen to as well.
Okay, I'll write it down. Thank you. No worries.
Okay. Does anyone have any more questions or anything they want to add about their
own, you know, experience being a Dom or even being a sub?
Is there a course on being a sub, like, coming up?
Or there's one on the website, right? Yeah, there's a course all about submission
on the website. So about you being the sub yourself.
So you can read into that one as well. Because maybe that would be more fitting
for you if you feel as though... I don't know.
Or maybe not. I don't know. Who knows? But at least you've got the information on
it. You've got a bit more of an idea. Does anyone do, like, both?
Or it's, like, do people do both? Or do they generally, like, stick to one more?
You can do both, for sure. You can switch, as they call it.
So I know that Elle, she used to do more sub.
But then she switched and does more Dom. And I think now...
I don't know. I think she maybe does both now.
But you can definitely switch, yeah, for sure.
And that's not... Just because you are a Dom doesn't mean you can switch and be a
sub. Because I like to be a Dom on cam. And I like to be a Dom in some other areas
of my life. But then in the bedroom, I like to be a sub.
So it's one of them. Like, you can switch between the both, you know.
You can tell your clients that. No. Probably not.
I think it's the biggest secret ever. Yeah.
I'm actually a sub. But the thing is, like,
I actually have told them, like, I would Dom...
Sorry, I would sub for the right guy, but it's not you.
Like, I've told them, like, you know, it's you.
But I wouldn't have subbed for the right guy.
And they would like that even more. Because then they're like, you know, it makes
them... It's even less for them. She's not actually gonna do it for me.
But, you know, she does do that. I don't know.
So yeah, you can tell them. It's not like just because you're a Dom, like, you could
never, you know, be a sub. Yeah. And
yeah, Elle wrote, she has switch in her username and she does both.
So she actually... Has. I think it's like Ruby switch or something like that.
Um, so that's like in a title. So the guys know she does both depending on the client
or day, maybe depending on how she feels.
Yeah. Does anyone have any more questions?
And by the way, if you don't have any more now, but something comes to you, just
always know you can reach out to me. Um, um, yeah, just let me know.
And, um, okay then I think we'll wrap that up for today.
Thank you everyone for coming along. I hope that was, um, beneficial for you all
and you learn something new. Um, but yeah, thanks again, girlies.
That's fun. Let me know how you put this into practice.
Um, I'd love to know, like really, really would love to know how you're getting on
and just also just to leave you with something like, even after doing it for 10 years,
I obviously still don't have all the answers.
Like, so, and I will, I will admit that to clients.
They all say, look, I don't really know much about that side of domination.
Tell me more. Cause as I said earlier, that are very specific kinks sometimes that,
you know, even after all these years, I still wouldn't have heard about.
So it's okay to not know and to tell your clients, I actually don't really know about
that. Can you tell me a little bit more? And then, you know, they can tell you and
then you can decide from then on if you want to offer that or not.
So, um, yeah, even though you do want to learn about this and learn about, you know,
what the different things are, and we've learned about a few different types of domination
today, the most popular, it's still okay to not have all the answers and to like
actually admit that to your subs. You know, you don't have to always know.
Um, but yes, that is us. Thank you so much for coming along and
I hope you all have a lovely evening and, um, yeah.
See you on the next call. My darlings. Oh, thanks Jay.
Thank you. Great call. Yeah. Thank you.